var questions = [{
    "question": "What is Hodor's real name?",
    "option1": "Wiley",
    "option2": "Wally",
    "option3": "Wade",
    "option4": "Wylis",
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question": "What did Hodor do before it was his job to carry Bran?",
    "option1": "He was a chef in the Stark kitchen",
    "option2": "He was a butcher's boy",
    "option3": "He was a stable boy",
    "option4": "He was a jester",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "Judging by their stay in the abandoned mill, what is Hodor afraid of?",
    "option1": "Rats",
    "option2": "Thunderstorms",
    "option3": "Ghost",
    "option4": "White Walkers",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "Does Hodor have any relatives at Winterfell?",
    "option1": "No, he's an orphan",
    "option2": "Yes, he's the secret son of Ned Stark",
    "option3": "Yes, he's Old Nan's great grandson",
    "option4": "Yes, he's Osha's distance relative",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "When Osha sees Hodor naked, what does she say?",
    "option1": "\"He's a big lad\"",
    "option2": "\"He must have giants' blood in him\"",
    "option3": "\"Seven 'ells!\"",
    "option4": "\"Put some clothes on Hodor!\"",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "When does Bran first skinchange into Hodor?",
    "option1": "Out in the wilderness, to find food",
    "option2": "When they are being chased by wildlings",
    "option3": "Near Craster's Keep, to break his chains and save his friends",
    "option4": "To try and save his direwolf, Summer",
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question": "Where does Hodor have a scar?",
    "option1": "His back",
    "option2": "His right eye",
    "option3": "His neck",
    "option4": "His left shoulder",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "What did Hodor repeat in agony before he was killed by the White Walkers?",
    "option1": "\"Help! Help me Bran!\"",
    "option2": "\"Hold the door!\"",
    "option3": "\"Hold down the roof!\"",
    "option4": "\"Noooooo, nooooo!\"",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "What ability does Hodor have?",
    "option1": "Healing",
    "option2": "Superhuman physical strength",
    "option3": "Echolocation",
    "option4": "Immortality",
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question": "Kristian Nairn, the actor portrayed by Hodor, has what occupation while not filming Game of Thrones?",
    "option1": "Door stop woodmaker",
    "option2": "Beer specialist",
    "option3": "DJ/Producer",
    "option4": "Highschool football coach",
    "answer": "3"
}
]